<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kafka on h12</title>
    <link>http://h12.io/tags/kafka/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kafka on h12</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2012-2018, Hǎi-Liàng &#34;Hal&#34; Wáng; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 13:57:09 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://h12.io/tags/kafka/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>RealTest: real test environment for Go</title>
      <link>http://h12.io/project/realtest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 13:57:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://h12.io/project/realtest/</guid>
      <description>h12.io/realtest provides real test environment for Go unit testing, based on Docker.
Includes:
 Queue  Kafka cluster (with zookeeper)  Database:  MySQL MongoDB  Cache  Redis  Configuration service  ZooKeeper   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kpax: a modular &amp; idiomatic Kafka client in Go</title>
      <link>http://h12.io/project/kpax/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 13:36:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://h12.io/project/kpax/</guid>
      <description>Install go get -u h12.io/kpax  Talk I have given a talk about Kpax at Gopher Meetup Shanghai 2016. See the slides.
Design The client is built on top of Kafka Wire Protocol (i.e. low-level API). The protocol related types &amp;amp; marshal/unmarshal functions are automatically generated by wipro from the HTML spec).
(-) means to be done.
Sub packages  model is an abstraction model for request, response, broker and cluster broker is a lazy, asynchronous and recoverable round tripper that talks to a single Kafka broker cluster is a metadata manager that talks to a Kafka cluster proto contains both low level API and a &amp;ldquo;middle&amp;rdquo; level facade producer: fault tolerant high-level producer (batching and partitioning strategy) consumer: fault tolerant high-level consumer (consumer group and offset commit) log: replaceable global logger cmd  kpax: command line tool to help with Kafka programming   Compatibility Compatible with Kafka Server 0.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>